Sukriti Kapoor

sukritikapoor@hotmail.com · +919560925239 · 01126191606 · H-25, Green Park Extn., New Delhi - 16

INTRODUCTION

I've been a keen writer of poems and essays since I was a child, and my passion for writing turned into love when I joined the Editorial Board of my school. It encouraged me to then start participating in MUNs as a part of the International Press. It further drove me to study mass communication and dive into the field of journalism with all hands in. Apart from writing, I love reading novels and poetry and, have a keen interest in history and psychology.

EDUCATION

B.A.(H) Multimedia and Mass Communication

Indraprastha College for Women, Delhi University Currently studying in second year

SSSCE - CBSE XII

The Mother's International School
Graduated in June, 2015 Aggregate of 93%

SSCE - CBSE X

The Mother's International School Passed in April, 2013 9.0 GPA

ACHIEVEMENTS

Honourable Mention in International Press

Sanskriti Model United Nations 2014

Second Position in Indigenous Music

The Mother's International School Talent Fiesta '12

Second Position in Bulletin Express

The Mother's International School Talent Fiesta '11

TECHNICALSKILLS

Experienced with Microsoft Office Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Publisher, and Adobe Photoshop. Familiar with Adobe Illustrator and Final Cut Pro.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Freelance Content Writer

Drill Maps, February 2016–present
Create content for website and patent to be filed at the US Patent Office.

Creative Writer and Contributor

Baatein, April 2016–May 2016

Developed creative content for social media platforms and helped in brand marketing.

Consultant

Unifiers Social Ventures Pvt. Ltd., 2015–present Create content for their magazine, Skilled, and edit participant and training manuals.

Intern

Press Trust of India, December 2015–January 2016 Interned at the Business Desk for four weeks.

EXTRACURRICULARS

Secretary, August 2016–present Member, 2015–present

Oghma, The English Editorial Society
Indraprastha College for Women, Delhi University
Organize various events and ensure society's
contributions and functioning, along with publishing
the annual college magazine.

Member of English Editorial Board

The Mother's International School, 2013–2014
Developed content for and contributed in publishing the annual school magazine, Navchetna.

Editor and Member of Lyceum

The Mother's International School, 2013–2015 Edited and published the first annual magazine of my school humanities' forum, Lyceum, and actively participated in related events.

Chief Editor of International Press, MISMUN

The Mother's International School, 2013–2015